Headlights hum like a hymn in the rain
I got a map with a burn on the corner and a pocket full of apologies
A rusted ring and a dead man's number still calling me in my sleep
You said, baby, you don't need saving
I said, I know, but I still pretend
Now I'm two lanes deep in the nowhere
With my shadow in the passenger seat again
Every mile markers a warning sign
Every radio song's a crime
Cause it sounds like you, sounds like you
I'm driving with a rally trap, hello
Sparking like sin in the night
Trying to outrun what I can't let go
But your name's in the tan line
There's a Bible in the glove box shaking
Next to a switchblade and a dime
I've been talking to God like a stranger
Every Saturday closing time
Your laugh was a match in the dark room
Lid up things I don't show
Now I'm mashed on the tongue of a hard truth
And the wind won't let me go
Three back roads, a broken vow
Every I'm fine is a blackout now
When it comes to you, comes to you
I'm driving with a rally trap, hello
Sparking like sin in the night
Trying to outrun what I can't let go
But your name's in the tan line
It's not the same, maybe I'm just a man
With a heart that won't stay in place
If you ever miss me, don't it, it'll only make it worse
Cause I'll turn this truck around and put us back